books.com.eg 2011-06-24

# Terms & Conditions

Welcome to Books.com.eg !! 

If you visit or shop at Books.com.eg, you accept ALL these conditions:

Please read them carefully. In addition, when you use any current or future Books.com.eg service or business you also will be subject to the guidelines, terms and agreements (Terms) applicable to such service or business. If these conditions are inconsistent with such Terms, the Terms will control.

Pricing  
Privacy  
Electronic Communication  
Copyright  
Return Policy  
Delivery & Shipping  
Payment & Security

Pricing:

Our pricing strategy is simply trying to get you the best deal. We offer discounts to most of our customers, specially our return customers. All prices include sales tax.

Privacy:

**What Personal Information About Customers Does Books.com.eg Gather?**  
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Books.com.eg. Here are the types of information we gather.

**Information You Give Us:**  
We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. Like your name, email, age…etc. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our store, and communicating with you.

**Automatic Information:**  
We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use cookies, and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Books.com.eg or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of Books.com.eg on other Web sites.

**E-mail Communications:**  
To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail from Books.com.eg if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers.

**Information from Other Sources:**  
We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

**What About Cookies?**   
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such as personalized advertisements, and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.  
The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Books.com.eg's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any Books.com.eg books and services that require you to Sign in.

**Does Books.com.eg Share the Information It Receives?**  
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. 

**Third-Party Service Providers:**  
We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions only, and they may not use it for other purposes.

**Promotional Offers:**  
Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of Books.com.eg customers based on a certain criteria.

**Business Transfers:**  
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, companies, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that Books.com.eg (Books for E-commerce, LLC), or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

**Protection of Books.com.eg and Others:**  
We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Books.com.eg, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**With Your Consent:**  
Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**  
We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.  
We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.  
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a **shared** computer.

**What About Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Websites?**  
Some parts of our site might include third-party advertising and links to other Web sites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party Web sites.  
These third-party Web sites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send (or serve) the advertisements that appear on our Web site directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party Web sites are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

**Are Children Allowed to Use Books.com.eg?**  
Books.com.eg does not sell books for purchase by children. We sell children's books for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use Books.com.eg only with the involvement of a parent or guardian.

ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS

When you visit Books.com.eg or send e-mails to us, you are communicating with us electronically. You consent to receive communications from us electronically. We will communicate with you by e-mail or by posting notices on this site and on the company's page on Facebook. You agree that all agreements, notices, disclosures and other communications that we provide to you electronically satisfy any legal requirement that such communications be in writing.

COPYRIGHT

All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, video clips, digital data, data compilations, and software, is the property of Books.com.eg (Books for E-commerce, LLC) or its suppliers or the publishers of the books offered and are protected by International copyright laws.

Returns Policy

You may return most new, unopened items that are sold and shipped by Books.com.eg within 14 days of delivery for a full refund BUT under one condition: ORIGINAL RECEIPT MUST BE AVAILABLE, either the printed receipt that you received with the shipment OR the receipt that you received electronically in your inbox after placing your order. We will also pay the return shipping costs only if the return is a result of our error. Items must be returned in their original book packaging. Most of our books come with Manufacturer's Warranty.

Delivery & Shipping

Shipping & Delivery is executed exclusively by ARAMEX; a global shipping & logistics services company. Also they collect cash payments from customers using the CASH ON DELIVERY payment option.

Payment & Security  
**Cash On Delivery Payment:**  
It is exactly as it sounds, you pay in cash when you receive the book. This service is only available to the Egyptian market for the time being and we will be looking forward to expand it to the Middle East & North Africa region.
